Simon Fraser Student Society fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Finance, 1966 - 1989; F-74-4; 18 cm of textual records
  - Budgets 2/2, 1966; F-74-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
  - Budgets, 1966 - 1967; F-74-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
  - Budgets, 1967; F-74-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1967; F-74-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1968; F-74-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1968 - 1971; F-74-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1969; F-74-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1969; F-74-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1969; F-74-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1970 - 1971; F-74-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1971; F-74-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Activity Fee, 1974; F-74-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Financial Statements, 1975; F-74-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Budgets, 1984 - 1985; F-74-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
  - Auditor's Report, 1989; F-74-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 74-20)
- Committees, 1965 - 1986; F-74-5; 21 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of committees associated with the Student Society. Included are committee appointments, correspondence and related material of the Anti-Calendar Committee, Departmental Student Unions Committee, Executive Committee, External Affairs Committee, Finance Committee, Frosh Orientation Committee, Medical/Health Services Committee, Presidential Search Committee, Services Commission, Student Court Judiciary Committee, Student Implementation Committee, Symposium Committee, and the University Centre Committee.
  Simon Fraser Student Society. Anti-Calendar Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Departmental Student Unions Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Finance Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Frosh Orientation Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Medical / Health Services Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Student Court Judiciary Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Symposium Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. University Centre Committee; Simon Fraser Student Society. Student Search Committee for an Acting Presdient; Simon Fraser Student Society. Services Commission
  - Committee appointments, 1970 - 1971; F-74-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Anticalendar Committee, 1965 - 1968; F-74-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Departmental Student Unions Committee, 1984; F-74-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Executive Committee, 1984 - 1986; F-74-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - External Affairs Committee, 1978; F-74-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Finance Committee, 1966 - 1976; F-74-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Frosh Orientation Committee, 1966; F-74-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Medical/Health Services Committee, 1965 - 1966; F-74-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1969; F-74-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Services Commission, 1984; F-74-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Student Court Judiciary Committee, 1968; F-74-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Student Implementation Committee, 1968; F-74-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Symposium Committee, 1966 - 1967; F-74-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - University Centre Committee, 1967 - 1968; F-74-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - UCB - Correspondence re Chaplaincy, 1965 - 1967; F-74-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence with Businesses, 1966; F-74-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence, 1968 - 1969; F-74-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence, 1970 - 1971; F-74-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence, 1972; F-74-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence re Food Services, 1972 - 1973; F-74-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Correspondence, 1974 - 1978; F-74-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Reports and Briefs, 1967 - 1981; F-74-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - UCB - Proposals for facilities, 1965 - 1967; F-74-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - small 74-34)
  - Minutes - UCB Board of Management, 1975 - 1976; F-74-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - small 74-34)
- Elections, 1966 - 1971; F-74-6; 4 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to elections for the Executive Council of the Student Society. Included are election rules, reports to council, correspondence, election results and related material.
  - Elections, 1966; F-74-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Elections, 1967; F-74-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Elections, 1968; F-74-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Elections, 1969; F-74-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Elections, 1970; F-74-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
  - Elections, 1971; F-74-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-21)
- Student unions, 1965 - 1991; F-74-7; 13 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of academic student unions. Included are publications, of the Archaeology Union, Computing Science Union, Economics and Commerce Union, English Union, Geography Union, Graduate Student Union, History Union, Languages Union, PSA Union, Psychology Union, and Women's Studies Student Union. Some Student Union files also contain the constitution, by-laws, and correspondence.
  Archeology Student Union; Computing Science Student Union; Economics and Commerce Student Union; English Student Union; Geography Student Union; Graduate Student Union; History Student Union; Languages Student Union; Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology Student Union; Psychology Student Union; Women's Studies Student Union
  - Archaeology Union, 1971 - 1982; F-74-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Computing Science Union, 1975; F-74-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Economics and Commerce Union, 1971 - 1982; F-74-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - English Union, 1974 - 1982; F-74-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Geography Union, 1970 - 1991; F-74-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Graduate Student Union Constitution, 1966 - 1968; F-74-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Graduate Student Union Correspondence, 1965 - 1973; F-74-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Graduate Student Union Newsletter, 1971 - 1973; F-74-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - History Union, 1969 - 1986; F-74-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Languages Union, 1969; F-74-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - PSA Union, 1969; F-74-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Psychology Union, 1970 - 1971; F-74-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
  - Women's Studies Student Union, 1979; F-74-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-22)
- Clubs and affiliated groups, 1965 - 1991; F-74-8; 68 cm of textual records ca. 250 photographs; Physical description: Photographs are found in sub-series 6, Outdoor club. 16 photographs, 20 slides located in F-74-8-6-11 112 photographs located in F-74-8-6-14 29 photographs located in F-74-8-6-15 49 photographs located in F-74-8-6-16 15 photographs located in F-74-8-6-17 13 photographs located in F-74-8-6-18 5 photographs located in F-74-8-6-19
  Series consists of records relating to Student Society sponsored clubs, and other affiliated groups. Included are club constitutions, club executive lists, club lists, club publications, and correspondence.
  The series is arranged into separate sub-series for each club or group.
  Further accruals are expected.
  Some published materials relating to individual clubs may also be included in series F-74-12, Publications.
  - Clubs general, 1966 - 1974; F-74-8-1; 8 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to SFSS clubs generally. Records include club constitutions, executive and membership lists, and publications, newsletters, and news releases of various clubs.
    Files were organized by the records creators by type of document (consitutions, membership lists, publications) rather than by club. Indiviudal files contain materials relating to a range of clubs.
    Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as stipulated by Archives policy or the donor. Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release and, as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the reference archivist for more details.
    - Club Constitutions, 1966 - 1970; F-74-8-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
    - Club Constitutions, 1967 - 1972; F-74-8-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
    - Club Executive lists, 1967 - 1971; F-74-8-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
    - Club lists, 1966; F-74-8-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
    - Club Publications, 1968 - 1974; F-74-8-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
  - Bookstore, 1967 - 1975; F-74-8-2; 5 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser Student Society Bookstore
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the operations of the Society's bookstore. The bookstore was established in 1966 and traded in used books. Records include correspondence, reports, and financial statements.
    Files arranged by the archivist chronologically.
    Simon Fraser Student Society Bookstore
    No further accruals are expected.
    Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as stipulated by Archives policy or the donor. Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release and, as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1968; F-74-8-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
    - Correspondence, 1970; F-74-8-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
    - Financial statements, 1974 - 1975; F-74-8-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-23)
  - Campus Radio, 1967 - 1991; F-74-8-3; 11 cm of textual records
    CJSF Radio
    - Constitution, 1969; F-74-8-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF, 1968; F-74-8-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Incorporation, 1968 - 1969; F-74-8-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Minutes, 1967; F-74-8-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Minutes, 1968; F-74-8-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Minutes, 1969; F-74-8-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Minutes, 1970; F-74-8-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Nominations for the Board, 1969; F-74-8-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Board Minutes, 1971; F-74-8-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Membership Lists, 1969; F-74-8-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Play lists, 1971; F-74-8-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence, 1968; F-74-8-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence, 1968 - 1971; F-74-8-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence - incoming, 1969 - 1971; F-74-8-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence - outgoing, 1969 - 1970; F-74-8-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence re: Applications, 1970; F-74-8-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence re: Applications, 1969 - 1970; F-74-8-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence re: Carrier Current, 1969 - 1970; F-74-8-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence with commercial stations, 1968 - 1971; F-74-8-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence with with CRTC, 1968 - 1969; F-74-8-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence re: FM, 1971; F-74-8-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence with Foreign Radio Stations, 1970; F-74-8-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence with Record Companies, 1970 - 1971; F-74-8-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence with Registrar of Companies, 1969 - 1970; F-74-8-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF Correspondence re: Resignations, 1968 - 1971; F-74-8-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CKSF "Indecent Proposal", 1971; F-74-8-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - CSFU "Report", 1977; F-74-8-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
    - Chronology and Essay by Tamas Revoczi, 1991; F-74-8-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 74-24)
  - Canadian Union of Students, 1966 - 1969; F-74-8-4; 15 cm of textual records
    Canadian Union of Students
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-8-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Publications, 1966; F-74-8-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-8-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Publications, 1967; F-74-8-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-8-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Publications, 1968; F-74-8-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Publications, 1968; F-74-8-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-74-8-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-25)
    - Publications, 1969; F-74-8-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Publications, 1969; F-74-8-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
  - Cinema Simon Fraser, 1975 - 1987; F-74-8-5; 2 cm of textual records
    Cinema Simon Fraser
    - Job description - Manager, 1975; F-74-8-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Publications, 1979 - 1987; F-74-8-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
  - Outdoor Club, 1965 - 1981; F-74-8-6; 19 cm of textual records
    Outdoor Club
    - Constitution, 1967 - 1968; F-74-8-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Executive, 1970 - 1979; F-74-8-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1979; F-74-8-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Membership and Telephone Lists, 1968 - 1975; F-74-8-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Log Book, 1967 - 1969; F-74-8-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Calendar of Events, 1979; F-74-8-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Canoe Race, 1968; F-74-8-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - Equipment Room, 1977; F-74-8-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - "The Voyageur" publication, 1965 - 1974; F-74-8-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-26)
    - "The Voyageur" publication, 1968 - 1974; F-74-8-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Whistler Cabin Log Book and Photos, 1968 - 1973; F-74-8-6-0-11; Physical description: 70 photographs (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Whistler Cabin - Correspondence, 1966 - 1974; F-74-8-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Ephemera, 1981; F-74-8-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Photograph Album, 1968; F-74-8-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Photographs - Canoe race, 1968; F-74-8-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Photographs - Canoe race, 1968 - 1977; F-74-8-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Photographs - Canoe race and bathtub race, F-74-8-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Photographs - hiking, F-74-8-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Photographs - Whistler cabin, F-74-8-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - SFU Outdoor Club general, vol. 1, 1973 - 1979; F-74-8-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - SFU Outdoor Club general, vol. 2, 1973 - 1979; F-74-8-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
  - Science Fiction Society, 1970 - 1981; F-74-8-7; 4 cm of textual records
    Science Fiction Society
    - "Spectre Analysis", 1970; F-74-8-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-27)
    - Newsletter, 1971 - 1974; F-74-8-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - "The Gamester's Guide", 1978; F-74-8-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - "Vulcan Mail", 1981; F-74-8-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - "Vulcan Mail", 1981; F-74-8-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
  - Miscellaneous groups, 1971 - 1991; F-74-8-8; 4 cm of textual records
    Chinese Students' Association; Simon Fraser University Musicians' Association; Simon Fraser Public Interest Research Group; Vancouver Women's Caucus; Snake Hill Food Coop
    - Chinese Students' Association, 1991; F-74-8-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - Musicians' Association, 1981; F-74-8-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - SF-PIRG, 1983 - 1990; F-74-8-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - SFU Women's Caucus, 1971 - 1974; F-74-8-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - Snake Hill food co-op, 1973; F-74-8-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
  - Economics Club, 1966 - 1967; F-74-8-9; 13 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the founding of the SFU Economics Club and the first two years of its activities. Records include meeting minutes of the Executive and General Meeting, the club's constitution, correspondence and reports, invoices and budget preparation papers, and blank letterhead, stationery and membership cards.
    Files are arranged chronology.
    Economics Club
    Records were transferred to the Archives in 2012 by one of the club's original founding members who had custody of the material.
    - Minutes of Executive, 1966; F-74-8-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-33)
    - Minutes of General Meeting, 1966; F-74-8-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-33)
    - Correspondence and meeting minutes, 1966 - 1967; F-74-8-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-33)
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1967; F-74-8-9-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-33)
    - Economics and Commerce Club, 1966 - 1967; F-74-8-9-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-33)
    - Club stationery, [ca 1966 - 1967]; F-74-8-9-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-33)
- Subject files, 1965 - 1984; F-74-10; 44 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to a number of issues, activities, and areas of interest to the Student Society. Includes correspondence, reports, publications, and ephemera on a wide range of topics such as Amnesty International, Drugs, Library Services and Parking. For a list of names that appear in file titles, see Access Points.
  Amnesty International; Canadian Association of University Teachers; Foster Parents Plan; Frontier College; Peak Publications Society; Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology; Shell Canada Ltd; World University Service
  - Amnesty International, 1966 - 1970; F-74-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Blood Drive Clinics, 1965 - 1966; F-74-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Blood Drive Clinics, 1967 - 1968; F-74-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Bulletin Boards, 1970; F-74-10-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - CAUT investigation 1/2, 1968; F-74-10-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - CAUT investigation 2/2, 1968; F-74-10-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Drugs, 1968 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Foster Parents Plan, 1965 - 1967; F-74-10-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1966; F-74-10-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Freedom Square Plaque, 1967 - 1968; F-74-10-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Frontier College, 1966 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Health Services, 1966 - 1967; F-74-10-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Housing, 1966 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-30)
  - Legal Services, 1969 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Library Services, 1969 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Liquor License, 1969 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Parking, 1968 - 1970; F-74-10-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - The Peak, 1965 - 1969; F-74-10-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Peak Publication Society, 1970 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - President's Ball, 1965 - 1967; F-74-10-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Press Release, 1966 - 1967; F-74-10-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Press Release, 1966 - 1984; F-74-10-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - PSA controversy, 1969 - 1976; F-74-10-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - PSA strike, 1969; F-74-10-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Second Century Week, 1967; F-74-10-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Questionnaire on Student Politics, 1969; F-74-10-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 74-31)
  - Selling on Campus, 1967 - 1970; F-74-10-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - Shell controversy, 1966; F-74-10-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
    Access review (Mar 14, 2023) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
  - Student activism, 1968; F-74-10-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - Student demands, 1968; F-74-10-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - Student consumer organization, 1969; F-74-10-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - Student Employment, 1970 - 1971; F-74-10-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - "T.A." Incident, 1967; F-74-10-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - University Awards, 1967 - 1969; F-74-10-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - University Centre Building, 1970; F-74-10-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - World University Service of Canada, 1969 - 1970; F-74-10-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - Yearbook, 1966 - 1969; F-74-10-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
  - Defense Fund for 114 Arrested Students (Administration Building sit-in), 1968; F-74-10-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 74-32)
- Publications, 1965 - 2009; F-74-12; 22 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the Student Society and its affiliated groups. Includes student almanacs and handbooks, Society bulletins and newsletters, newspapers affiliated with the Society, journals, directories, guides, event flyers, notices, and posters.
  The series was arranged into sub-series by the archivist. It was established in 2012 to replace the former series F-74-9, Publications. This had been a single series (no sub-series), originally arranged alphabetically, but with subsequent accruals the order was no longer in sync. To facilitate access, the archivist re-organized the material into sub-series, with files in each organized chronologically.
  All files are open, with one exception in sub-series 3; see the sub-series description for details.
  - Publications – general, 1965 - 2009; F-74-12-1; 12 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of publications of or funded by the Society and its clubs. Titles include newsletters of SFSS or affiliated clubs (Council Bulletin, SFU Science Undergraduate Society's Purple Period / Purple Publication, International Club Newsletter); literary or campus opinion reviews (Compass, the first issue of SFU Literary Magazine edited by Brian Fawcett and Henk Suys, Cheap Thrills, International Skyline, Makar, SFU Komix); and newspapers funded by SFSS (Identity – SFU Canadian-Persian Student Newspaper, Mountain Echoes – BC Student Multicultural Newspaper, and U-Voice – SFU Chinese Student Newspaper). Note that most titles are represented by only one or two issues. However, the sub-series does include fairly complete runs of the Council Bulletin over 1966-1967 and U-Voice from 1998-2009.
    Material in this sub-series was formerly incorporated into series F-74-9; it was re-organized by the archivist in July 2012.
    All files are open with no access restrictions.